fullqurandownload.com 2013-09-27

# Full Quran Download: privacy policy

###  privacy policy 

**Introduction**  
---  
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.fullqurandownload.com  
   
  **Information Collection and Use**  
  
[fullqurandownload.com ](http://www.alquranic.com/) information on our website  collected from  some others site. We will not sell, this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. No individual information about any visitor will be released to any third party without that visitors permission. The information collected for free used so people can benefit form our website   

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
   
**Links**  
  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [fullqurandownload.com ](http://www.alquranic.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.  
  
If you have any questions about the security at our website,   

**Notification of Changes**  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
